# **Ayowale Oluyomi Ojo**

Lagos, Nigeria | +2348131593204 | Ojoayowale3@gmail.com

#### **EDUCATION**

**Lagos State University** Lagos, Nigeria Bachelor's Degree (part-time) in progress **Grace Polytechnic** Lagos, Nigeria 2019 Associates Degree **New Horizon** Lagos, Nigeria CCNA & CompTIA N+ 2018 **Ogunmodede Senior High School** Lagos, Nigeria High School Certificate 2017

### **Profile Summary**

Ayowale Oluyomi Ojo is a Front end developer who has worked with HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, Javascript, PHP, MYSQL, JQuery, SQL, Databases, MongoDB and React for more than 3 years. Exceptional at converting designs and wireframes into high-quality code.

#### WORK EXPERIENCE

**Lifted Netcom** Maryland, Lagos

Front End Developer

2019-2022

- Partnered with design, product, back-end teams to take clients wireframes from conception to implementation creating multiple web products and apps.
- Assisted the development team in maintaining and creating websites some of which were hosted on GITHub pages allowing customers repositories to be hosted directly.
- Worked independently remotely and in person to solve problems and complete assigned tasks involving frontend web development including (HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, Javascript, Jquery, React,).
- To collaborate, solve problems, and complete tasks, I used remote tools such as Slack, Google Meet, and Zoom.
- Developed end-user training documentation and conducted training sessions.

**3T Consulting (SIWES)** Lekki, Lagos

Networking Engineer

2018-2019

- Participated in the task of troubleshooting and designing networks for companies and clients.
- Worked with devices like switches routers access points and firewall.

**Macom's Ventures** Epe, Lagos Feb 2017- 2018 Data Entry Clerk

• Performed large volume data entry, having high speed with 99.9% accuracy.

- Highly proficient with the use of Microsoft Excel and Google sheets for data entry.
- very attentive to detail oriented as I was in charge of crosschecking input data against original enteries

Responsible for producing monthly financial reports, adding closing balances to new month and
organizational charts using advanced Excel spreadsheet functions to support business operations and
improve office organization.

## **LINKS**

- Portfolio Website => <a href="https://starboyzs.github.io/portfolio/">https://starboyzs.github.io/portfolio/</a>
- Github Repository => <a href="https://github.com/Starboyzs">https://github.com/Starboyzs</a>
- Linked-in => https://linkedin.com/in/ayowale-ojo-39934122a

## **Certifications**

• Web-Development => Web development certificate of completion

## **SKILLS & INTERESTS**

- Front-end web development
- Back-end web development
- Python
- Javascript
- Flutter&Dart
- CCNP
- Microsoft excel.
- Customer support.
- IT support.
- Phone and Laptop repair